Stop arguing with me about the humanist elements of Israeli society.
The society itself is not.
It is not humane.
It is not egalitarian.
It is not democratic.
None of it.
Everything it exists in is a falsehood and a projection.
And you can tell this because anybody in that society who exists as a humanist, who wants egalitarianism and who acknowledges that this ain't a democracy is shunned.
Anybody in that society who breaks from their complete devoid of humanity is actually attacked verbally and often physically.
So don't tell me about the but not all Israelis because that's not the point.
The point is that their goal is that all Israelis operate in that mindset.
One devoid of humanism.
And that is not an opinion.
That is literally their actions.
Also, just stop arguing with me.
We are stardust floating up.